<Patch>
  
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="Clawer" or defName="Woodmaker" or defName="Berrymaker" or defName="Medicinemaker" or defName="VDE_Nectarmaker"]/displayedStats</xpath>
    <value>
      <li>PlantWorkSpeed</li>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="Barkskin" or defName="VDE_Stonedigger"]/displayedStats</xpath>
    <value>
      <li>MiningSpeed</li>
      <li>MiningYield</li>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="Medicinemaker"]/displayedStats</xpath>
    <value>
      <li>MedicalTendSpeed</li>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="Clawer"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A dryad caste specialized in aggression and damage-dealing attacks. The clawer dryad is named for its massive claws. Though it can do tremendous damage, it is vulnerable to attacks itself.\n\nThe clawer dryads can also harvest crops in nearby fields. It will not harvest wild plants.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="Woodmaker"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A slow, bumbling caste of dryad which specializes in wood production. Together with its Gauranlen tree, this dryad can generate a wood-like material on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.\n\nIt can help grow most types of trees in farm areas.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="Berrymaker"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A dryad caste specialized in food production. Together with its Gauranlen tree, this dryad can generate nourishing berries on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.\n\nIt can help grow most food plants.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="Medicinemaker"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A dryad caste specialized in medicine production. Together with its Gauranlen tree, this dryad can generate medicinal herbs on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.\n\nIt can help grow medical plants and some drugs.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="VDE_Nectarmaker"]/description</xpath>
    <success>Always</success>
    <value>
      <description>A dryad caste specialized in nectar production. Together with its Gauranlen tree, this dryad can generate nectar on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.\n\nIt can help grow some types of plants.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/GauranlenTreeModeDef[defName="Barkskin"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A dryad caste specialized in absorbing hits during combat. Barkskin dryads are covered by a thick bark-like hide which is partly formed by the Gauranlen tree itself. Under human influence, it can act as a damage-absorbing fighter.\n\nIt will sometimes help out with mining.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

</Patch>